<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hacking to the Gate</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hacking to the Gate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:29:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Log File2</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/log-file2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:29:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/log-file2/</guid>
      <description>Here we go again&amp;hellip; Okay, I screwed up. Although I know I should lock in and build stuff, I failed miserably. About a few months ago, I even posted it on X about my plan before the end of the year. Of course, it has fallen apart.&#xA;I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t excuse myself, but I still want to write down what have happened lately so that I can reflect on it, learn my lessons, and hopefully move on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log File1</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/log-file1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 23:50:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/log-file1/</guid>
      <description>So Far So Good? Since I get back into learning mode, I have been doing pretty well. I even started doing Advent of Code, and I have fun doing it. However, it&amp;rsquo;s not all rainbows and butterflies even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now regained my ability to really focus for at least a few hours each day. So, what&amp;rsquo;s the problem?&#xA;The Problem! The problem is actually twofold. On the one hand, I still have trouble with doing the work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log File0</title>
      <link>https://example.org/posts/log-file0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 14:43:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/posts/log-file0/</guid>
      <description>A New Start Time flies, and it&amp;rsquo;s already December 1st. Since this is the beginning of a new month, I want to make some changes to how I approach learning in order to make this month counts. Yes, even though this is the last month of 2024, I just want to size the time I have to actually take my study seriously so that I can become a better version for my next role.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
